<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <title>
      Advertising
    </title>
    <body>
        Note: We have not yet started advertising on our website, but we are currently accepting inquiries and application from potential advertisers. If you are interested in advertising on our site, please fill out the contact us form that can be found in the footer.

        OUR ADVERTISING GOAL:

        - Give the maximum exposure and bang for the money to our advertising partners.
         &amp;
        - Give our members/visitors highly relevant and valuable advertisements.

        You may have heard the saying, what you get is what you paid for. Well, we have taken this saying to a whole new level. With us, you will get a lot more bang out of your precious advertising bucks than what you pay for. By the time you finish reading this section, we are sure that you will agree with us. We make every effort to give our advertisers the best return on their advertising investment.

        WHY ADVERTISE WITH US?

        We firmly believe that our success lies in our advertiser’s success.

        If you ask why you should advertise with us, well, we’d like to ask you why not advertise with us. Here’s why you should advertise on our website and not miss on this premium marketing opportunity for your business.

        We live in a digital era where technology is changing faster than what we can cope up with. Some of the traditional forms of advertising, such as advertising in newspapers and magazines, are becoming almost non-existent due to continuously declining circulation and readership. With the increasing use of ad-free boxes and digital recorders, most people either watch ad-less television shows or record and watch them by conveniently skipping the ads. This changing trend is decreasing the effect of television ads significantly. The so called sponsored pay-per-click or cost-per-impression internet advertising is inundated with fraudulent or irrelevant clicks and very short visits. This makes the sponsored ads mostly cost-inefficient.

        However, our advertising model is most efficient and least expensive way of advertising. It is optimized to maximize the advertiser’s ROI. We charge a fixed cost per fixed period of time in which you will get unlimited impressions and clicks. We also guarantee a minimum number of impressions. So say goodbye to fraudulent clicks and say hello to fraud-free advertising. What you see is what you will get. Moreover, there are absolutely no hidden costs or fine-prints.

        When you become our ad partner, we will not only give you online ads, but we will also put you in our trusted list of partners. We will also give you access to upgrade your profile and posts. We will also write an exclusive review on our website which will always stay live and be shown under featured reviews. Moreover, as our ad partner, you will also have full access to our website where you can write article, blogs, and participate in community forums. As per recent studies, blogs and forums are some of the most important factors in creating brand awareness and even increasing sales figures. Best of all, everything will be search engine optimized for all major search engines so that you get even more exposure and traffic.

        So, when we combine the power of online banner and contextual ads with featured profile of your company, featured review of your company, and premium access to other tools on our website – it’s surely the right formula to give the right kind of exposure to your products and services.

        WHY ADVERTISE WITH US, INSTEAD OF OTHER SOCIAL NETWORKING WEBSITES?

        A very common question that may come to the mind of any potential advertisers is why they should advertise on our website instead of other more popular and bigger social networking websites. Well, the answer is quite straightforward. The main reason is that our website caters to a very distinguished niche audience, not necessarily mass audience. And, oh yes, we forgot to mention that you can get a better coverage on our website for a fraction of what you would pay elsewhere. Furthermore, it all depends whether you want to be a small fish in a big pond or a big fish in a small pond. So, seize this opportunity and make the right choice.

        MOST HONEST &amp; TRANSPARENT:

        We are proud to say that we are one of the most honest and transparent websites on the world wide web. We never buy bulk traffic or lure people to visit our site or become our member. Most websites (even some of the biggest names in the industry, but we won’t take any names here) boast of heavy traffic, most of which is not even relevant to the industry to which they belong to. They then make a very colorful and attractive media kit with full blown graphics and charts displaying all their numbers. In fact, many of the popular sites have phishing and spyware so that they can install a cookie on your computer to collect personal information. Most users don’t even come to know about these things. We don’t indulge in any such practices. No annoying pop-up, no spyware, no malware, no phishing. We have even been contacted several times to buy dirt cheap traffic which will definitely make our figures look a lot more attractive to advertisers, but we have already turned them down. But don’t get us wrong. We do want to popularize our site, but we like to adhere to most ethical ways in doing so, which results in most relevant traffic for our advertisers, and most pertinent content for our members. To take matters one step forward, we show the most accurate statistics to even our visitors, not just the advertising or marketing managers of other companies. This is why we are so proud of being what you can call the most honest and transparent site in the industry. With us, you will get the most relevant exposure and most pertinent traffic for your business.

        SOME OF MANY BENEFITS OF BECOMING OUR AD PARTNER:

        - Logo and Brief Profile Placement on our Partner Page: Placement of your company logo along with a hyperlink and brief profile in our media partner page under the specific partner category.

        - Image + Text Ad: Placement of your ad image with text on almost every page of our website.

        - Banner Ads: Placement of your banner ad on the header or footer part of our website.

        - Premium/Featured Review: Premium review of your company placed in the featured review section of our website where other users can forward, save, rate, like, comment, and share on social media.

        - Premium/Featured Profile: Premium profile of your company placed in the featured profile section of our website where other users can forward, save, rate, like, comment, and share on social media.

        - Posts/Comments: Access to making unlimited posts and comments.

        - Special Discounts: Additional special discounts of 10% on our other forms of advertising and promotional options.

        - Brand Equity: Build brand equity and awareness by partnering with a premiere name.

        Note: The above benefits will be valid only during the term of our partnership.

        ispace! Copyright © 2020	Facebook	LinkedIn	Pinterest	Instagram	Twitter	Youtube	EZ solutions
        About
        Partners
     </body>
  </Item>
</Items>

