<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <title>
      Announcements
    </title>
    <body>
        ispace1.com - 1 space for everyone!

        i1 network – the way to connect and share with others!

        the next generation of online networking

        everything combined on one unified platform

        We are not just into reconnecting with your old contacts.. we are more about discovering and connecting with new ones.. we have combined the best of social and professional networking into one like never before.. we are more than just a simple networking website.. we want to provide an open platform where our users can connect and share with each other in many different ways.

        If you want to “just” reconnect with your long lost friends, make connections for professional purposes, post short thoughts hundred times a day, post a blog or an article, look for a date, this may not be the best place for you; but, if you are looking for all of the above and much more by discovering new connections and gaining access to many other networking tools, you are at the right place, come right in.

        ENDLESS POSSIBILITIES:

        Inside, you can look and search for, or connect and share with, a friend, an acquaintance, a pal, a buddy, a companion, a date, a soul mate, a roommate, a housemate, a teammate, a playmate, a travel-mate, a study-partner, a life partner, an employer, an employee, an accomplice, an associate, a collaborator, a business partner, a new business opportunity, or just express and share your views on some of the hottest trending topics, or give yourself or your business the exposure it needs, or simply browse through some great profiles and postings, whatever you want to do, the possibilities are endless on our website, there is no beginning and there is no end, there are no boundaries and there are no walls, its’ one endless space, it’s one infinite space, it’s my space, it’s your space, it’s everyone’s space, it’s one space for everyone.

        OUR FOUNDING PRINCIPLES AND CORE VALUE SYSTEM:

        Our Mission: “Our mission is to offer multiple ways of networking to everyone all over the world.”

        Our Vision: “Our vision is to provide a fair and open networking environment where everyone can express their views.”

        Our Objective: “Our objective is to give everyone extraordinary networking tools and exposure.”

        Our Promise: “Our promise is to present everyone with a safe and friendly networking experience.”

        Our Goal: “Our goal is to take online networking to a whole new level and we want our users to experience the next generation of networking like never seen before.”

        In short, we pledge to work relentlessly to make our website one of the finest web-addresses on the world-wide-web!

        OUR STORY:

        The story behind ispace1 is really simple. Our founder, Raja Surya, wanted a platform where people and organizations can connect and share with one another in multiple ways, both at a social as well as professional level. He searched the breadths and depths of the internet and couldn’t really find even a single website that would fill this need in a somewhat meaningful way, at least not in a way he had envisioned. This is what prompted him to start conceptualizing this idea and this is how this website came about – from a small concept to a premium platform. We think we are still warming up and are going to bring to you a whole new experience with online networking – good, better, best; we will never rest till our good becomes better, and our better becomes the best.

        OUR COORDINATES:

        We started off from a tiny shed in the backyard of our family house (no, not a garage) and as a matter of fact, we still have one of our offices there. While we take the liberty to think that we have a presence where each one of you is located, in your hearts and minds, our main control center is in the Silicon Valley of California, with satellite offices in some other places.

        PHILANTHROPY:

        We are formed on the founding principles that we want to make this world a better place. With that in mind, we have plans to undertake various initiatives in the coming time as we proceed with our endeavor. We plan to get involved in a diverse range of social issues. We also have plans to donate a portion of our revenues to charity and also to sponsor children in under-developed countries. Since we are just getting started, it would be too early to lay down any specifics. Please be sure to check back later for more updates.

        CONTRIBUTIONS:

        There is absolutely no cost to become a member, and to make use of most of our online services. Since we are privately funded, we’d appreciate if you wish to become a donor to support our efforts. Your contribution will immensely help us in carrying forward our endeavors to provide great services and also to continue enhancing our website to make it more helpful to our users. We will greatly appreciate your contribution, but you are under no obligation to do so. Regardless, you can make full use of our website at no cost to you.

        There is one more way you can contribute without spending a penny. You can help us spread the word and get your friends and family to become our members. You can also help us by filling all the details in your profile and by posting more content. Both of these things will help us immensely and neither one will cost you anything. We know it very well that there is nothing we can do without you. We also know that we are nothing without you. We need your patronage. We need your help.

        We are one-hundred percent debt-free and credit-free as our website is completely privately owned and operated. This gives us total control over everything. Neither are we backed by any type of venture capital, nor do we have any type of bank loans. Several entities have contacted us for equity participation, but so far we have been trying to maintain a business model that would feed itself.

        We hope that we can sustain on our own with the help of our valuable members and partners. We certainly look forward for your support and patronage so that we can continue to deliver world-class services to you.
    </body>
  </Item>
</Items>

