<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <id> </id>
    <title>Ways To Find Online Love Or Romance1</title>
    <description>10 Ways To Find Online Love Or Romance By Joining Some Of The Most Popular Websites And Apps That Can Help You Find The Love Of Your Life</description>
    <body>
      Love is the purest and most pious form of emotion or feeling, which is a profoundly tender passionate affection and genuine care for another person without any expectations or selfish motives, still it is so vague yet so simple, as it includes physical, emotional, romantic, intimate, and spiritual closeness between two souls, leading to ultimately divine and heavenly happiness and pleasure.

      Love has to be experienced as it can’t be explained in mere words, so the best way to know what its actual meaning is by falling in love

      Love is the best and most innocent type of emotion a person can ever feel because to love and to be loved in return gives a feeling of goodness and contentment.

      Love ignites a very strong liking and attraction between two people.

      Love ignites deep romantic and sexual desires.

      Love is a feeling of warm personal attachment.

      Love is the most desirable form of emotion.

      Romance is a vehicle or a medium to express love and care for someone, implying a manifestation of one's deep and strong feelings or emotional desires to connect with another person, both intimately as well as romantically, making it the most expressive and pleasurable feeling originating from a physical and emotional attraction between two people, and tends to be usually associated with romantic and sexual desires.

      Romancing is making the other person feel special and desirable and it is reciprocated in the same manner.

      Romance can be in many different ways and it varies from person to person.

      Romance ignites or excites a relationship and take it to the next level.

      Romance is also a way of showing love and affection towards a person.

      Romance is one of the key components of any relationship that can keep it alive.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
      <author>
        <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
        <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
      </author>
      <author>
        <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
        <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
      </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Romance2</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Romance</description>
    <body>
      Love and romance are almost used synonymously. The main reason is that both terms are often used in the same context. However, both love and romance are different words and it’s important to know the differences between them. Knowing there difference will better equip you with having success with both.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and romance.

      Love is a profound feeling that people have for each other; whereas, romance is the vehicle through which those same feelings can be more easily expressed.

      Love is a fiction and has no physical presence as it’s invisible; whereas, romance is a reality that can be demonstrated by doing real life things.

      Love is a feeling that comes straight for the heart and it can only be felt without any explanation; whereas, romance is a gesture such as giving res roses and candle lit dinners that helps in expressing love for another.

      Love has no specific language and it’s hard to interpret it; whereas, romance has the ability to convey excitement and exhilaration.

      Love is an inward feeling of attraction and commitment; whereas, romance is an outward expression of the what one wants to express.

      Love is a feeling between two people; whereas, romance is a tool that can be used to enhance and the bonding between two people.

      Love is the initiator of a relationship; whereas, romance keeps a relationship alive by reinforcing it and reigniting it time and again.

      Love can be of many different kinds; whereas, romance can only be intended as romantic love which is also a type of love.

      Love is an intense and affectionate feelings for another person; whereas, romance makes those feelings actual by giving it a physical shape and form.

      Love is a plant that grows with time; whereas, romance is the vase that helps love to be nurtured and grow even stronger with time.

      Love comprises of mind, body, and soul; whereas, romance stresses more on the body aspect and thereby brings the mind and soul together.

      Love is more of an emotional need; whereas, romance is more of a physical need.

      Love stays even after romance is over; whereas, romance seizes to exist at some point or it at least becomes less relevant after a certain period of time.

      Love is one of the most unexplainable things and it needs to experienced; whereas, romance can be  easily explained as well as experienced.

      Love needs romance for it to last for a long time; whereas, romance has no prerequisite need for being in love.

      Love is the result of romance; whereas, romance may or may not turn into love.

      The fact of the matter is that both love and romance are important parts of having a successful romantic relationship. Love brings purity and selflessness while romance concretize those feelings. Love and romance both creates a very powerful attachment and bonding between two people. Both must coexist and are equally important to sustain a relationship. It is almost impossible to have a strong relationship without one of these traits. Love leads to romance. Romance leads to love. Both love and romance results in an everlasting relationship.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Like3</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Like</description>
    <body>
      Love and like are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and like:

      Love is more permanent and long term as it is a deep attachment and care for a person; whereas, like can be more temporary in nature.

      Love consists of strong emotional as well as romantic feelings; whereas, like may or may not involve any romantic or emotional feelings toward the other person.

      Love is intended to be a lifelong commitment; whereas, like has no commitment component attached to it.

      Love has inherent presence of lots of sacrifices and compromises; whereas, like may or may not have any sacrifices or compromises.

      Love has like inbuilt in it; whereas like does not need to have feelings of love.

      Love is strong and deep attachment for the other person; whereas, like has no requirement of being attached to the other person.

      Love overlooks all superficial qualities and is pure as well as selfless; whereas, like is usually based on attraction or care for the other person.

      Love is blissful and may or may not involve any commitment; whereas, like has no place for any commitment.

      Love originates from initial like for a person; whereas, like may or may not result in love for the other person.

      Love happens automatically and effortlessly; whereas, like for a person may be because of physical attraction, intelligence, social status or any other quality which a person might possess.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Lust4</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Lust</description>
    <body>
      Love and lust are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and lust:

      Love is an intense feeling of affection and care towards another person; whereas, lust is purely sexual in nature.

      Love comes from long term commitment and feelings that keeps on growing with time; whereas, lust is a strong desire that is sexual in nature.

      Love is above and beyond sexual pleasure; whereas, lust is basically a temporary feeling of mutual sexual enjoyment or pleasure.

      Love can last for a lifetime; whereas, lust may dissipate with the passage of time.

      Love may include lust; whereas, lust usually does not include love.

      Love is seen as a positive feeling; whereas, lust is seen as a negative feeling.

      Love is more on the emotional side; whereas, lust is purely physical in nature.

      Love with a little bit of lust can spice up a relationship; whereas, lust without any love is purely sexual with no emotions or feelings at all.

      Love is an important element of everlasting relationships; whereas, lust can just make the relationship more lively.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Infatuation5</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Infatuation</description>
    <body>
      Love and infatuation are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and infatuation:

      Love is a genuine long term feeling of intense affection for another person without any selfish reasons; whereas, infatuation is being carried away by unexplainable short term passion or sexual attraction.

      Love brings in a committed relationship; whereas, infatuation may or may not bring in any committed relation.

      Love is a warm feeling of attachment for the other; whereas, infatuation is being unsure about one's affections even if they are strong.

      Love is being sure about their affection which may lead to commitment later on; whereas, infatuation is a short term obsession which can lead to love later on.

      Love never fades away; whereas, infatuation fades away as soon as a better match is found.

      Love is a matured emotion; whereas, infatuation usually comes at a tender age and is immature.

      Love is a permanent emotion; whereas, infatuation is temporary madness for the other person.

      Love is the final outcome of initial infatuation; whereas, infatuation is the initial affection towards another person which may or may not lead to a higher level of love.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Obsession6</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Obsession</description>
    <body>
      Love and obsession are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and obsession:

      Love is a genuine feeling towards another person, one that is selfless and it usually doesn’t go away with passage of time; whereas, obsession is a camouflage of being overly compulsively preoccupied with someone and it usually fades away with time when true feelings begin to emerge.

      Love involves attachment, sacrifices, care, affection and support; whereas, obsession is a strong desire for the other person and can be sometimes be considered as insane.

      Love may be one or two sided; whereas, obsession is usually a one sided desire or attachment for the other person and it can even become dangerous or violent.

      Love is one of the purest forms of feelings; whereas, obsession is more of a disorder.

      Love is selfless and has no motives except giving happiness to the other person; whereas, obsession mainly involves one’s selfish motives and has not place for happiness of the other person.

      Love tends to be more balanced and in control of one’s senses; whereas, obsession leads to total loss of balance and control.

      Love makes the world go round and it is the main ingredient to make one happy in life; whereas, obsession is more of a crazy act.

      Love with just a little bit of obsession may be a good things as it keeps the emotions alive between a couple; whereas, obsession ultimately kills the love that may once be there between two people.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Crush7</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Crush</description>
    <body>
      Love and crush are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and crush:

      Love is a feeling filled with genuine emotions and care for a person; whereas, a crush is more superficial in nature.

      Love is a feeling that goes very deep and is very strong; whereas, a crush is a very shallow feeling that appears only on the surface.

      Love is usually more permanent feelings; whereas, a crush is just a very temporary liking for a person where one gets carried away in matter of seconds.

      Love usually doesn’t dissipate very easily; whereas, a crush usually goes away as fast as it sets in.

      Love is strong attachment for the other person; whereas, a crush may not involve any attachment.

      Love is usually more pure and goes far beyond any superficial attributes; whereas, a crush is usually due to good looks or any other physical attributes of a person.

      Love is a beautiful feeling and can last forever; whereas, a crush is usually short lived and goes away very fast.

      Love may be one sided or both sided; whereas, a crush is always one sided.

      Love takes one to the higher level of relationship; whereas, a crush tend to end without any progression unless it transforms into something more meaningful.

      Love is a meaningful emotion; whereas, a crush is nothing more than a secret admiration for the other.

      Love cannot transform into a crush; whereas, a crush may transform into love.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Fling8</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Fling</description>
    <body>
      Love and fling are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and fling:

      Love is a serious and permanent emotion as it is more stable in nature and it usually stays for a very long time and even forever; whereas, a fling is like a passing thought which comes and goes away in a very short time.

      Love consists of very high level of emotions; whereas, a fling is highly unstable and may not have any substance behind it.

      Love is everlasting but fling; whereas, a fling is usually fun romantic relationship for a short period of time.

      Love may consist of commitment; whereas, a fling is when two parties are attracted towards each other knowing that it would not result in any sort of commitment.

      Love is a beautiful feeling as the entire world seems beautiful; whereas, a fling also may bring the same magnitude of feelings but only for a short period of time.

      Love always becomes very painful when hearts are broken; whereas, a fling may or may not become painful depending on the degree of care and affection the two people shared between each other.

      Love may result from a fling; whereas, a fling cannot come out of true love.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus Care9</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Care</description>
    <body>
      Love and care are perhaps two of the most confusing words. Most people use them almost interchangeably. There is a clear and profound difference between the two words. One must be clear about the difference when these words are used together or separately. Not being able to understand the difference will lead to all sorts of relationship difficulties with someone special.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and care:

      Love is a feeling that can’t be explained. It is an immense larger than life kind of a feeling. The feelings are so strong that it becomes difficult to be control. It is an unforgettable yet unexplainable feeling.

      Care is a concern for someone. The concern can be due to liking or some other interest in that person. It is more of an act of compassion or friendliness. It is something that can be felt for close friends and family and even for a stranger.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and care:

      Love is a very strong attraction towards someone, whereas care comes out of concern or liking for someone.

      Love can only be felt for someone special in your life of the opposite sex, whereas care can be felt for almost anyone of either sex.

      Love is generally instinctive as it happens naturally without making an efforts, whereas care is more of a well thought of voluntary act of kindness.

      Love means the other person holds a very important place in your life, whereas care has more to do with friendship without any place in your heart.

      Love is matter of heart and it happens on its own, whereas care is only related to kind heartedness of a person and is more about being humane.

      Love is a voluntary action as it happens almost automatically, whereas care is a voluntary choice because that is morally and ethically the right thing to do.

      Love exists in a very personal relationship with someone special, whereas care can exist without any personal relationship as it can be even for a stranger walking on the street.

      Love is a long-term commitment which is intended to last a lifetime, whereas care is usually for a short-term and usually ends with the wellbeing of the other person.

      Love is mostly driven by physical desire or personal needs, whereas care is rooted in more genuineness.

      Love must include care in it for it to be meaningful, whereas care does not need any feelings of love in it for it to exist.

      The above are the main differences between love and care. They are different but still close related to each other. Love and care are two different emotions, yet they are part and parcel of the same thing. They don’t necessarily have to occur together. But when they do, that’s what leads to a successful long-term relationship. Love and care are both required for a relationship to work.

      In fact, feelings of care makes us able to love someone. If you can’t care for anyone, then it will be hard for you love someone. That’s why all seek a person who places high value for care. When you are in love, your heart will tell you it’s love as you will get drawn towards the other person. If you just care for someone, you won’t have any feelings beyond the care aspect.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love Versus In Love10</title>
    <description>Main Differences Between Love And Being In Love</description>
    <body>
      Love and in love are part and parcel of the same emotion and they are almost inseparable, yet they mean two different emotions and sometimes it becomes difficult to distinguish between them.

      Following are some of the main differences between love and in love:

      Love is when someone chooses to love someone and is a well thought out and planned emotion which never dies; whereas, being in love happens automatically without making any efforts whatsoever.

      Love is selfless and usually demands nothing in return; whereas, being in love comes with a lot of expectations from the other person.

      Love may last forever; whereas, being in love may one day result in falling out of love.

      Love is a great emotion; whereas, being in love makes it even better.

      The best way is to love and be in love with that person at the same time.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love And Attraction11</title>
    <description>Love And Law Of Attraction Are Two Sides Of The Same Coin</description>
    <body>
      Love and attraction is the action or ability to evoke interest, pleasure, desire, or liking for someone or something. Attraction is the powerful magnetic force that pulls two people together regardless of their own will which may be avoidable but often impossible to ignore because it keeps coming back. Romantic attraction is physical as well as emotional attachment to a person. Attraction can also be non-romantic, where there is plain friendship between two people when they don't quite love each other but they definitely like each other a lot.

      Attraction is a natural phenomenon as people gets drawn to others. But, falling in love with someone solely on the premise of physical attraction can be a big mistake. According to the reward theory of attraction, people like those whose behavior is rewarding to them. Anticipation in attraction can alone increase liking.

      Attractiveness surely helps create a positive first impression. It helps in getting noticed by others which could be a stepping stone to something greater. This first impression and the initial attraction play an important role in all sort of interpersonal relationships at all levels. It is like that because people like being associated with the ones they are most attracted to.

      Attractiveness goes much beyond just the physical attributes as it also takes into account the personality of the person as well as how they carry themselves and their nature or even sense of humor. Of course, other things such as status, earnings, and the like, also make a big difference when it comes to attraction. So romantic attraction is a combination of many different things some of which may be totally superficial. Many individuals are not good looking but they are immensely attractive where everyone just gets drawn towards them.

      Love and attraction are directly correlated. The more one loves someone, the more attractive they find that person. Moreover, the more in love people are, the less attractive they find other people of the opposite sex to be. The law of attraction is the magnetic magical power that draws similar energies together and even the law of gravity is part of the law of attraction. It attracts thoughts, ideas, people, situations and even circumstances.

      The law of attraction spreads through thoughts, by being attracted to similar people or ideas. It is the law and power that attracts and brings two people close to each other. This law can be used to attract love and be more attractive to the opposite sex. Where there is no attraction there is no love.

      Attraction is the first emotion for people who fall in love with each other. Attraction is very necessary to be in a love relationship. Attraction leads to love and love leads to more attraction. Attraction in love is a cycle.

      Love is an attachment between two people and attraction is liking between two people. Attraction can be between any two people but love happens between two people who love each other and want to be with each other forever. Of course, attraction is one of the most important element of love. Without attraction, love will eventually fade away or it may not even start.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Love And Jealousy12</title>
    <description>Love And Jealousy Are Inseparable When There Is Possessiveness</description>
    <body>
      Love and jealousy are part and parcel of any romantic relationship. Feeling of jealousy are as normal as the feeling of love. What matters more is how one acts and reacts to it. That’s what makes the world of difference. Romantic jealousy is usually triggered when one of the partners display or even hint a romantic interest in another person.

      Jealousy has long been often believed to be the guardian of love. But in actually, it is mostly the reason for the downfall of love. Jealousy may not always mean that one doesn’t trust someone. It just means that there is so much of love and care for that person that they are scared to lose the other person, either partially by losing attention or even fully.

      Love and jealousy are both emotions or feeling. It’s how one feels about another person, which can be hard to describe in words. Love and Jealousy go hand in hand. Jealousy is one of the emotions of love. It is healthy to be jealous but it should not go to the extremes.

      Jealousy creates a feeling of insecurity of losing the person. Such feeling is necessary to keep the love strong. However, too much jealousy can rob the freedom of the other person. It can create conflicts and arguments and is a threat to a relation.

      Love jealousy can also sometimes be used to get your love back. More the jealousy, more the love showered by the partner in the fear of not losing that person. The word jealousy technically refers to the feelings and thoughts of fear, insecurity, concern, and anxiety over a foreseeable loss of someone of great personal value. Jealousy often consists of a mix of emotions such as anger, resentment, inadequacy, and helplessness.

      Jealousy should not be confused with envy, though many people use the two terms synonymously. Jealousy is a human reaction that all humans are born with. Jealousy has been observed even in infants five months and older. Jealousy is not a culture-specific phenomenon as it exists in all cultures, though it may be more prevalent in cultures than others.

      Jealousy is a concept explored by many people from different walks of life.

      Psychologists have come up with various concepts of processes causing jealousy and have classified reasons that may result in jealousy.

      Sociologists have validated that it is mainly the cultural values and beliefs that play a vital part in defining what actually activates feelings of jealousy.

      Biologists have demonstrated elements of human body that may unintentionally inspire jealousy.

      Artists have toyed with the jealousy theme in songs, movies, plays, poems, books, folkdances, puppet shows, photographs, paintings, sculptures.

      Theologians have proposed their own religious opinions of jealousy in light of the scriptures of their respective faiths.

      Romantic jealousy originates from sociobiological factors, cultural and historical factors, personality factors, relational factors, situational factors, and strategic factors.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Everlasting Love13</title>
    <description>Everlasting Love That Last Forever And Ever</description>
    <body>
      Everlasting love is love that lasts forever, usually a lifetime. It is eternal and goes on until eternity. It has no expiration date and goes on indefinitely until death. It is endless and it never ends no matter what hurdles or obstacles come. It is continuous without interruptions and is unbreakable. It is not dependent on any external force. Nothing in the world can break it.

      Everlasting love is of course very rare to find it but one must cherish it if they ever get it. It is usually both sided but may also be one sided. Both parties stand by each other till the end in spite of many hurdles. The couples can also be addressed as made for each other when the love is everlasting. It grows stronger and stronger as they age together. It happens only when two people are truly committed and devoted to each other.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <title>Emotional Love14</title>
    <description>Emotional Love That Is Purely Sentimental</description>
    <body>
      Emotional love is love that is purely based upon emotions and feelings for one another. It may or may not be based upon any other variables such as physical looks, financial status, education, and the like. It may also not require romantic or sexual involvement. If two people are bound to each other primarily because of emotions, then their bonding or relationship becomes much stronger and is more likely to sustain for a longer period of time.

      Emotional love develops because of similar characteristics or circumstances or qualities between the two partners. When two partners face similar circumstances they tend to bond emotionally. When both partners enjoy each other's company, they tend to look upon for each other at every good or bad moments of life. It’s when that person would be the first person to come in mind for every emotional moment, whether it's sad or happy for whom emotional love has been developed in the heart. It’s mostly mental rather than physical. It’s one of the major elements that bonds two people together because when two people are bounded by emotions then the love becomes strong as they support each other in all adverse situations of life. After all, a love with emotions is more sustainable than love without emotions.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Intense Love15</title>
    <description>Intense Love Is Extremely Strong</description>
    <body>
      Intense love is love that is extreme in degree and amount. It is extremely deep as well as devotional. Everything about it is excessive and immoderate. It is a very powerful, passionate, forceful, and deep form of love that is exceedingly strong. Its intensity is so strong that nothing can break it or even reduce its being.

      Intense love is also very ardent, fervent, and can even be fanatical in nature. It is so strong that people start doubting the sanity of the person involved. It is when another person's happiness becomes more important than their own. When either one of the parties or both can go do anything and everything for each other. It is love beyond any limitations. The feelings are also very intense and acute. It is very rare to find such kind of love these days.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Unconditional Love16</title>
    <description>Unconditional Love That Has No Conditions</description>
    <body>
      Unconditional love is unrestricted and unreserved. It is absolute love without any terms and conditions or any stipulations of any kind. It doesn’t change with situation or circumstances. It is also known as affection without any limitations or boundaries. It is complete love. It doesn’t demand or even ask for any love back from the other person.

      Unconditional love is selfless love that is not based on how the other person treats or behaves. It is very rare to have such type of emotions or affections for another person. It is selfless love without any motive. It demands nothing in return from the other person. It does not change with time or circumstances or distance. The feelings for their partner never changes no matter what. It is the greatest gift one can give to each other. It is like loving someone beyond one's limits. It can take love between two people to the highest level. It also comes with a lot of compromises and sacrifices.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Blind Love17</title>
    <description>Blind Love That Is Ignorant Of Everything Around</description>
    <body>
      Blind love is love when one is blinded by one or multiple faults or imperfections in a person. It is when physical appearances makes no difference. Even social status or any other issue makes no difference whatsoever. It is when even any obvious shortcomings that are visible to others are often overlooked or totally dismissed.

      Blind love can be so overwhelming that one doesn’t realize what’s going around in the world. They start seeing perfections even in imperfections. It makes either or both partners completely insane. They both accept each other just the way they are, completely and wholeheartedly.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Mutual Love18</title>
    <description>Mutual Love Is Common And Shared Between Two People</description>
    <body>
      Love is a highly volatile feeling, especially when it’s one-sided and not mutual. Mutual love is two-sided love. Mutual love is reciprocated love. It is common and joint love between two people.

      Mutuality in love is a basic element in any healthy romantic relationship. Secured relationship calls for mutuality so that two people are working towards a common goal, which is to make their relationship work for the long-haul as a couple. Mutual love can surpass anything. Many couples come together after a breakup when there is mutual love.

      Mutual love brings equilibrium in a relationship since the love of each partner for the other is equal. Mutual love gives security and assurance because both partners love each other in the same way without any selfish motives. Mutuality in relationship consists of a few basic elements for it to nourish. Mutuality in relationship means mutual love, mutual affection, mutual trust, mutual support, and mutual goals.

      Mutual love helps in making a relationship grow more solid as both partners feel loved and respected equally. Mutual affection gives rise to a feeling of mutual warmth and fondness for each other. Mutual trust in each other leads to a more honest and transparent relationship. Mutual support for each other in good and in bad times gives a feeling of being there for each other unconditionally. Mutual goals is the total sum of everything as both partners make all efforts to reach the same and common destination.

      When you combine all of the above things, it results in mutuality in every way, emotionally, physically, sexually, mentally, spiritually, and realistically. The first step is to realize the importance of mutuality in love and the second step is to proactively work towards it. If there is inequality or unfairness in a relationship, it is more likely to eventually fall apart. Before you enter a relationship, it is a good idea to self-ascertain if you are actually ready for love and if you are willing to give what you expect from the other person.

      If you are in a relationship and if you want to build mutuality or reciprocity in your relationship, it is never too late. If you feel there is an imbalance in your relationship, it is very much possible to balance it before one side goes down and the other up, just like in a measuring scale. Mutual love can be built by showing appreciation for each other. Mutual affection can be built by spending more intimate time with each other. Mutual trust can be built by agreeing with things in advance and specifying what exactly you can or can’t do. Mutual support can be built by backing each other in every way possible and especially in downtime. Mutual goals can be built by talking in advance about what you both want in life and in your relationship so that you both can vigorously work towards it.

      Mutuality in relationship can be easily attained by being open with your partner. It may be a good idea to lay out everything on a piece of paper so that you both know what is expected from you. If you feel there is inequality or unfairness in your relationship, it is important to communicate that to your partner. If you don’t do that, the gaps will become wider and eventually the thread that is holding you both together will break when it reaches the limits of elasticity.

      This problem can be very easily solved, the sooner you detect it and try to solve it, the sooner it will be solved. Remember, a healthy relationship requires mutuality, equality, parity, and reciprocity, or else it will die its own death when things go out of proportion.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Joint Love19</title>
    <description>Joint Love To Maintain A Positive Balance In Combined Love Account</description>
    <body>
      Joint love is like a joint bank account. Both partners deposit and withdraw love from the same account as when needed. It results in a big pool of love. The idea should be to grow the balance as high as possible. It is a joint result of both partners and they both have equal rights on it. Joint love gets even better when both partners contribute equally. If only partner is depositing and the other only withdrawing, then it will eventually reach a zero balance. The balance can only grow when both partners deposit more than they withdraw.

      Joint love is that love wherein both the parties work together to nurture and make their love strong. Where there is understanding and respect between a couple who stand strong with each other. Joint love is when you love someone and that love is reciprocated in a similar manner. Joint love is based on combined love, trust, and understanding in each other. Both partners act as strong pillars for each other, no matter what may be the circumstances. Joint love builds a long lasting relationship.

      Joint love is when two people respect each other and their decisions. Those who have never known the intense companionship of joint love have missed the best thing in life. Joint love is like heaven for two people who are in love with each other. The strongest relationships are built on joint respect and understanding. Joint love brings feeling of happiness together. Joint love is combined feelings between a couple. Joint love is never one sided. Joint love is when two people touch each other's soul. Joint love is when difference can be worked out.

      Joint love is beating of two hearts together in unison. Joint love is combined love. Joint love is dual and two sided. Joint love is cooperative. Two people in a joint relationship are joined together by the strongest adhesive in the world and they can never be pulled apart until eternity, regardless of the circumstances or surroundings.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Real Love20</title>
    <description>Real Or Pure Love Is Honest And Truthful</description>
    <body>
      Love itself is a very complex emotion, finding if it’s true is even more complicated. In fact, there is no sure-shot way to determine if what you are experiencing or if what you have in your relationship is true love or something else. We all want true or pure love but very few of us even know what it actually is. The definition of true love would differ from person to person, situation to situation. No two individuals are the same, no two relationships are the same, no two feelings of love are the same, no two romantic relationships are the same. If you want to know the meaning of true love, take a moment a think about what it means to you.

      Defining true love would be similar to defining a rainbow. You just have to see it to know how beautiful it is. No words can do justice to express how each color is so vibrant. Each person would define it differently. Likewise, you have to experience love to know what it actually is. The main reason it’s hard to define love is because we feel or experience love from our heart and soul, not from our brain or mind. Definitions are defined from mind, feelings are felt from heart.

      Real love is what is in our heart, soul, and spirit. The first step to experience real love is by opening your heart to love yourself. When you open your heart to love yourself, your heart gets filled with the love that is as ubiquitous or omnipresent as the air you breathe and the oxygen that pumps your heart. This is what true love is, the filling of the emptiness or hollowness within you that assures you that you are never alone. When we love ourselves, we become more welcoming to loving and getting loved without any selfish motives.

      Real love in a romantic relationship is when two people open their hearts that is already filled with love. Their love grows many folds when their love overflows from their hearts for one another. Love is known to become bigger when it is shared. This is real love. It is a magical feeling that can only be felt by the two people and even they can’t express what it really is. Real and pure love is divine, it’s God.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>True Love21</title>
    <description>True Or Honest Love Is Actual And Factual</description>
    <body>
      True love is honest. True love is actual. True love is factual. True love is pure. True love is pious. True love is dedication. True love is sacrifice. True love is unconditional. True love is a prayer. True love is the best form of love.

      True love stands still. True love is not affected by circumstances. True love is giving unwavering support. True love is total acceptance. True love is a song. True love is selfless and generous.

      True love is when you care for the wellbeing, health and happiness of the other person more than your own wellbeing, health and happiness. When you think of your partner's happiness more than your own. When all your thoughts, words, and actions are according to your partner's needs. True love is when you know the negative side of a person and you still want to be together with that person for the rest of your life.

      True love is like accepting the person just the way they are. True love is when you find perfection in imperfection. There is nothing that needs to be changed about another person to become lovable. The people who love truly will never leave you, regardless of the circumstances. True love is when you try to do things for your partner which you would not otherwise. True love is compromising and to accepting your partner as it is without asking them to change. True love is about being a real supporter to collectively reach your goals with your partner. If you want true love in your life, just be true to yourself and to others.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Sexual Love22</title>
    <description>Sexual Love Is Sensual And Erotic</description>
    <body>
      Sexual love is purely sexual, as the term suggests. It is a strong and deep feeling of sexual desire and attraction. Sexual love is love which arises out of sexual craving and to be intimate with each other. It may also include emotions and other love feelings but they don’t have to.

      Sexual love is when sexual feelings occupy the major space in one's heart and all other emotions and feeling either don’t even exit or if they do then they take a backseat. It’s when sexual passion as its peak between two people and sexual connection is stronger than any other emotions such as bonding and attachment. Sexual love is purely physical in nature, although it may or may not involve real feelings of love. Such kind of love dies out as soon as the passion is gone because passion is the main foundation of sexual love. It feels extremely good but it has a short life.

      Sexual Love is that love when two people are bonded by feelings of lust and sex. Their association is limited to sexual connection. They can also be considered as sexual partners. Such love is more physical in nature then mental and emotional. It is the sexual and physical union with the lover.

      In sexual love, attachment and affection is based on sexual activities. In many couples sexual desire fade away after few years and the spice of the relationship dies. In such cases arousing of sexual desire becomes necessary to strengthen their relationship. Love between partners is not just mental connection, it includes sexual activities as well and keeping such activities alive is necessary. Of course, if sexual love is one small part of the whole package, then that’s the best combination. Sexual love makes the overall love stronger because it is a main part of any relationship.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Obsessive Love23</title>
    <description>Obsessive Love Is Extreme And Fanatical</description>
    <body>
      Obsessive love is defined as a theoretical state of mind in which a person feels an irresistible and excessive obsessive desire to own or retain another person toward whom they feel a strong attraction. When one or both the parties in love are obsessive for each other, it is said to be obsessive love. Obsessive love is intense and extreme degree of love. Obsessive love is usually one sided.

      Obsession is the domination of one's thoughts or feelings by a persistent idea, image, or desire. Obsessive love is when one or both people have a strong desire for the other and such want is so strong that it feels like some mental illness or disorder. When one or both partners are obsessively attracted towards  each other, it is called as obsessive love. Obsession is an impulse that forces its way into consciousness and is associated with mental disorder. It is a strong attraction or desire for the other.

      Obsessive love is never desirable as it does not create healthy relationship and environment if it is one sided. Being obsessed takes away the freedom of being in relationship with each other as one or both the parties tries to dominate the other. Obsession is like being possessive of the other person to an extent that it robs the freedom to live happily in a good environment. Obsessive love is when one person feels a compulsive desire to be with another person. The feelings of infatuation or liking become so extreme that it becomes obsession for the other.

      Obsessive love can be taken as a symptom of mental defect or irrational thinking. It becomes hard to accept failure or rejection to possess the love of that person. Obsessive love is often time categorized as a mental illness, but it is not officially termed as a mental disorder. Obsessive lovers often feel total inability to contain their extreme acts such as violence toward themselves or the other person.

      When obsessive love becomes too extreme, it may involves violence, where one person tries to physically harm themselves or the other person. They wholeheartedly believe in their feelings of love, and often discard the notion that their crazy obsession is not real love. Obsessive love involve consistent thoughts of wanting every part of that person, be it spending time with that person or not letting that person see anyone else. Obsessive love is feelings of infatuation that are exaggerated and inflated, intensifying to the point of becoming obsessive.

      Obsessive love may have addictive qualities as well. They isolate themselves from everything else and just focus on their love object to an extent that they lose the ability to do any other work. It love can be treated by psychotherapy and counseling can also help. Obsessive love has been glorified and romanticized in literature for centuries and ever since mass media came into existence.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Perfect Love</title>
    <description>Perfect Love Is Flawless And Faultless</description>
    <body>
      We are human are trained to seek perfection in everything, but we often forget that there is nothing like perfect. Likewise, there is nothing like perfect or imperfect love. Some people are perfectionist and they see perfection in everything so much so that they want to see perfection in their love too. Sounds foolish but yes there are some people who seek perfection in love too.

      Some people are very specific about everything they want in their partner. If one of them is a perfectionist and the other is not, then it leads to conflicts and fights and lots of disagreements. Perfect love looks for everything in perfection right from proposing to being together. They want perfect gifts for the perfect occasions. Perfect dress for the perfect events. Perfect timings of words and phrases and the list is endless.

      The reality is that perfect love doesn’t exist. It may appear that two people are perfectly in love, but that’s not the case. Love is a sentiment that can be grown for ever and ever, it can never reach perfection because there will always be room to make it better. People who look for perfection in love or a perfect love partner ends up in solitude because they are looking for something that doesn’t exist. Another way to look at this is by thinking that perfect love as the one that is perfect for us and not necessarily the whole universe.

      Love is a beautiful emotion but it full of flaws. It’s the flaws that make love more interesting. A perfect flawless and faultless love would be dull and boring as it would seem more like a robotic love. We humans are all imperfect and so is the love we feel or want from another person. So stop thinking about perfect love and think about what will make your love more pleasant and irresistible.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>

  <Item>
    <id></id>
    <title>Unbreakable Love</title>
    <description>Unbreakable Love Is Indestructible And Indissoluble</description>
    <body>
      Love is a fragile feeling that can be broken with just a little tap. Love is so sensitive that it has to be handled with care or else it can break into pieces very easily. However, unbreakable love is a love that can’t be broken. Unbreakable love is impossible to break and can withstand anything. Unbreakable love is that love, which can never be broken or separated regardless of the circumstances. The partners stand by each other until the very end of life. Their love for each other is so strong that nothing can break it.

      Unbreakable love is rare to find. The partners of unbreakable love keep their promises and never say goodbye until death do them apart. Unbreakable love is so strong that nobody can sow the seeds of hatred in them. They remain united forever. Their love for each other grows stronger with each passing day. Such couples are said to be made for each other. Only death can separate them. Unbreakable love is true love in the real sense.
    </body>
    <image>/images/astrology-horoscope/heartbreaks-breakups.png</image>
    <date>11-16-2019</date>
    <authors>
     <author>
      <authorName>ispace1</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.ispace1.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    <author>
      <authorName>Raja Surya</authorName>
      <authorLink>https://www.google.com</authorLink>
    </author>
    </authors>
  </Item>
</Items>
