<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <title>
      Cookie Use
    </title>
    <body>
        COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS:

        Note: In this document “The Website” refers to “ispace1.com”.

        COOKIES:

        WHAT IS A COOKIE:

        A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. It allows us to recognize you as a User when you return to the “The Website” using the same computer and web browser. Like most websites, we use cookies and web log files to track site usage and trends, to improve the quality of our service, to customize your experience on “The Website”, as well as to deliver “The Website” and third-party advertising to Users both on and off the “The Website”. In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing the Services to our Users, we may allow certain authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through cookies will not be personally identifiable but may provide general segment information (e.g., your industry or geography, career field, or information about your professional or educational background) for the enhancement of your user experience by providing more relevant advertising. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. “The Website” does not store unencrypted personally identifiable information in the cookies.

        TYPES OF COOKIES:

        Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A session cookie is used to identify a particular visit to the “The Website”. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Cookies on our website do not link to or store your personal information. A persistent cookie is set once you’ve logged in to your “The Website” account. The next time you visit the “The Website”, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing User so you will not need to log in before using the Services. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number) or to send a message to another User, however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. For example, when you sign in to our website, we will record your user or member ID and the name associated with your user or member ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file, if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. For security purposes, we will encrypt any usernames, passwords, and other user or member account-related data that we store in such cookies. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from our website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of our site, content and advertising. Other technology like Macromedia’s flash can be used to place the functional equivalent of a cookie on your computer. You can control flash “local stored objects” or “flash cookies” using the Macromedia Website Privacy Settings Panel at www.macromedia.com. “The Website” may use cookie-equivalent technology for the limited purpose of enhancing the security of “The Website’s” services. We do not use flash cookies for advertising purposes. We may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver (such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.), and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies and provides information about this behavioral advertising practice (www.networkadvertising.org).

        COOKIES AND USE OF COOKIE DATA:

        When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. During your visits to other websites where we advertise, we (or third parties) may use certain data collected on our site to show you the type of “The Website” advertisements likely to be of greater interest to you. Although you may not opt out of receiving online advertisements generally, you may control the collection of data on our site used for targeted “The Website” advertising during your visits to other websites.

        DELETING COOKIES:

        Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings. (Click "Help" in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions.) If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser, but in some cases doing so may impact your ability to use “The Website”.

        OPTING-OUT OF ADVERTISING COOKIES:

        You may opt out of our data collection for use by third party ad companies to provide targeted advertising to you when you visit other sites. Cookies are unique to each computer. Therefore, you must opt out separately on all computers you use. If you delete all of your cookies (specifically, the "Opt-Out" cookie), you will have to go through the opt-out process again to reactivate your opted-out status.

        WEB BEACONS:

        WHAT ARE WEB BEACONS:

        Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on the web pages (or in email) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

        HOW WEB BEACONS ARE USED:

        We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or email messages to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website visitors to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities. To support the Services we provide at no cost to our Users, as well as provide a more relevant and useful experience for our Users, we target and serve our own ads and third-party ads both on and off the site using ad networks. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad exchanges, ad technology vendors and research firms. We target ads to Users based on general profile categories (e.g., “product managers in Texas”) or on non-personally identifiable information inferred from a User’s profile (e.g., industry, current or former company, school, compensation bracket, gender, age, ethnic origin, nationality, or other aspects of your life) in addition to a User’s use of “The Website” or their clicking on “The Website” ad inventory. “The Website” does not provide personally identifiable information to any third party ad network. We use ad technology such as web beacons, pixels, anonymous ad network tags, and cookies to more effectively serve ads to our Users on and off “The Website” through ad networks, as well as to collect anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers. Because your web browser requests advertisements and web beacons directly from ad network servers, these networks can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to our site from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website. Third parties may use anonymous information about your visits to our site and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You may opt-out of ads served to you off “The Website”. If you opt-out you may lose certain functionality of the “The Website” Services, as well as the potential benefit of receiving ads that are targeted to your interests which, in turn, may limit your ability to fully realize the benefits of the “The Website” Services to build and leverage your professional network.
    </body>
  </Item>
</Items>
