<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <title>
      Copyright Policy
    </title>
    <body>
        Note: In this document “The Website” refers to “ispace1.com”.

        “The Website” wishes to present a platform where our Users share honest and precise information. We value the intellectual property rights of others and wish to offer a website which contains no content that violates those rights. Our User Agreement requires that information posted by Users be accurate, lawful, and not in violation of the intellectual property rights of third parties. To promote these goals, “The Website” provides a procedure for submission of such complaints regarding content posted by our Users. Our policy and procedures are explained in the following sections of this document.

        In accordance with our User Agreement, and regardless of whether “The Website” may be liable for any alleged violation of rights or inaccurate or unlawful content, “The Website” may fully or partially remove or disable access to specified content appearing on “The Website” upon receipt of a verified notice asserting that the content infringes intellectual property rights, is inaccurate, or is otherwise unlawful. Whether or not we remove content or disable access, “The Website” may make a good faith attempt to forward the written notification, including the complainant’s contact information, to the User who posted the content and/or take other reasonable steps to notify the User that “The Website” has received notice of an alleged violation of intellectual property rights or other content violation. The User may refute a claim by submitting a counter-notice as permitted in these procedures. Any counter-notice submitted may be provided to the complainant with the User’s contact information. Our policies and procedures for removing or disabling access to content alleged to be infringing, inaccurate or otherwise unlawful are and remain at our sole discretion. It is also our policy, in appropriate circumstances and in our discretion, to disable and/or terminate the accounts, temporarily or permanently, of Users who may infringe or repeatedly infringe the intellectual property rights of others, or who otherwise post inaccurate or unlawful content. Kindly note that any notice or counter-notice you submit must be honest and must be submitted under penalty of perjury. A fake notice or counter-notice may result in personal liability; you may hence wish to look for the recommendation of legal counsel prior to submitting a notice or a counter-notice.

        CLAIMS REGARDING COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT

        You may not post, distribute, or reproduce in any way any copyrighted material, trademarks, or other proprietary information without obtaining the prior written consent of the owner of such proprietary rights.

        Pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (17 U.S.C. § 512), “The Website” has implemented procedures for receiving written notification of claimed infringements. “The Website” may also designate an agent to receive notices of claimed copyright infringement. Without limiting the foregoing, if you believe in good faith that your work has been copied and posted on the Service in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide us or our Copyright Agent with the following information:

        A. An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;

        B. A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;
        C. A description specifying the location on our website of the material that you claim is infringing;
        D. Your full name, postal address, telephone number and e-mail address;
        E. A written statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and F. A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.

        COUNTER-NOTICE:

        If you believe that a Notice Of Content and Intellectual Property Violations has been improperly submitted against you, or if you contest the removal of the allegedly infringing, inaccurate or unlawful content, you may submit a Counter-Notice, pursuant to Sections 512(g)(2) and (3) of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. You may complete the Counter-Notice Regarding Claim of Copyright Infringement form, or otherwise provide a written communication which contains:

        A. Your physical or electronic signature;
        B. Identification of the material removed or to which access has been disabled;
        C. A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that removal or disablement of the material was a mistake or that the material was misidentified;
        D. Your full name, postal address, telephone number and e-mail address, and that you will accept service of process from the Complainant submitting the notice or his/her authorized agent.

        Please submit your Counter-Notice to “The Website” Copyright Agent by email. Any assertions made by you in submitting this form are under penalty of perjury. “The Website” will process the Counter-Notice in accordance with its policies and procedures which remain in our sole discretion.

        CLAIMS REGARDING CONTENT AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY VIOLATIONS (OTHER THAN COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT)

        To notify “The Website” that you in good faith believe that content (“Specified Content’) posted by a User on “The Website” infringes your intellectual property rights (other than copyright, in which case please see Claims Regarding Copyright Infringement) or is inaccurate or unlawful, you may contact “The Website’s” Content Complaint Manager via email. Any assertions made by you in submitting this form are under penalty of perjury.

    </body>
  </Item>
</Items>