<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Items>
  <Item>
    <title>
      Plans
    </title>
    <body>
        UPGRADE YOUR ACCOUNT:

        For just a few extra bucks, you can take your personal or business profile to the next level to gain extra exposure by upgrading your account to a premium or featured account. It will cost you only a few bucks to upgrade your account. There is a minimum commitment required. This is a very economical and effective way to gain access to extra features and exposure. Please be aware that we only want a limited number of upgraded accounts, so make sure you grab your spot before we are sold out!

        HIGHLIGHTS: 11 REASONS TO UPGRADE YOUR ACCOUNT!

        - Send Message to Almost Anyone: all upgraded members can send message to almost anyone, paid or non-paid members.
        - Get Messages from Almost Anyone: all upgraded members can get messages from almost anyone, paid or non-paid members.
        - Appear More Often in Search Results: all upgraded profiles will appear more often in search results, more than regular profiles.
        - Get Higher Ranking in Search Results: all upgraded profiles will get higher rankings in search results, above regular members.
        - Access to Profile Views: Access to daily and monthly break-up of how many people viewed your profile, and to who all, when, and how many times others viewed your profile with their complete details
        - Access to Profile Appearances: Access to daily and monthly break-up of how many times your profile appeared in search results, and to top keyword searches for your profile and their respective counts

        Personal Account Paln
        FEATURE	REGULAR (FREE)	PREMIUM	FEATURED
        Make a full-blast personal/business profile	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Share any profile or article in social media sites	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Like any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Favorite any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Forward any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Post Updates	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send requests for connections	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send messages to connections	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send messages to non-connections	No	Yes = x	Yes = x
        Get message from regular members	No	Yes	Yes
        Appear more often in search results	No	More	Most
        Get higher ranking in search results	No	High	Higher
        Access to Profile Views	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to Profile Appearances	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to the list of who all favorited your profile	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to the list of who all liked your profile	No	Yes	Yes


        Business Account Plan
        FEATURE	REGULAR (FREE)	PREMIUM	FEATURED
        Make a full-blast personal/business profile	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Share any profile or article in social media sites	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Like any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Favorite any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Forward any profile or article	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Post Updates	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send requests for connections	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send messages to connections	Yes	Yes	Yes
        Send messages to non-connections	No	Yes = x	Yes = x
        Get message from regular members	No	Yes	Yes
        Appear more often in search results	No	More	Most
        Get higher ranking in search results	No	High	Higher
        Access to Profile Views	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to Profile Appearances	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to the list of who all favorited your profile	No	Yes	Yes
        Access to the list of who all liked your profile	No	Yes	Yes
        BENEFITS: WHY JOIN?

        Join: sign-up for free and create a personal/business profile

        Share: share profiles and postings with others

        Connect: connect with others

        Communicate: exchanges messages with others

        Follow: follow others and get followed by others

        Like: like and get liked by others

        Search: search for others and be easily found by others

        Post: make unlimited postings and be read by millions

        Track: track and follow interesting postings

        Albums: create multiple photo albums

        Control: control every aspect of your account

        Exposure: get exposure across the web

        Safe: free from viruses, spywares, phishing, malware

        Engage: get engaged with others in many different ways

        Free: All of this is totally free

        Upgrade: Upgrade to get access to premium features



        WHY UPGRADE?

        Send Messages to Almost Anyone: send messages to almost anyone, paid or non-paid members.

        Get Messages from Almost Anyone: receive messages from almost anyone, paid or non-paid members.

        Full Access to Profile Stats: get access to profile views: daily and monthly break-up of how many unique and total users viewed your profile, when they viewed it, and how many times they viewed it, with complete demographic details with graphs, get access to profile appearances: daily and monthly break-up of how many times your profile appeared in search results, and to top keyword searches for your profile with their respective counts.

        Extra Premium Features: get premium features such as read notification for sent messages.

        Priority Customer Service: get priority customer service.

        Special Icon in Profile: get a special differentiating proprietary icon in profile.

        Appear More Often in Search Results: appear more often in search results, more than basic profiles.

        Get Higher Rankings in Search Results: get higher rankings in search results, above basic profiles.
    </body>
  </Item>
</Items>

